https://proteomeconsortium.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Who we are
Our website address is: .
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Comments are closed.
Search
December 2020
M
T
W
T
F
S
Categories
2016 update of the PRIDE database and its related tools (2)
Antibody (37)
Antigen (3)
Assay Kit (28)
Cells (7)
Default (10)
Elisa Kit (22)
Enzyme (17)
Experimental data from flesh quality assessment and shelf life monitoring of high pressure processed European sea bass (Dicentrarchus labrax) fillets. (1)
HSD17B4, ACAA1, and PXMP4 in Peroxisome Pathway Are Down-Regulated and Have Clinical Significance in Non-small Cell Lung Cancer. (1)
Kit (21)
Lab Product (36)
Lab Reagent (36)
Lentivirus Vector (6)
Medium (5)
MINT, the molecular interaction database: 2012 update (1)
Monoclonal Antibody (5)
NATtrol (3)
Particles (9)
Pcr Kit (11)
Peptide (8)
Polyclonal Antibody (9)
Protein (11)
Proteomic analysis and interactions network in leaves of mycorrhizal and nonmycorrhizal sorghum plants under water deficit. (1)
Reagent (34)
Recombinant Protein (15)
RNA (27)
Serum & Plasma (6)
Solution (3)
The Gene Ontology Annotation (GOA) Database: sharing knowledge in Uniprot with Gene Ontology (1)
The ProteomeXchange consortium in 2017: supporting the cultural change in proteomics public data deposition (1)
The PRoteomics IDEntifications (PRIDE) database and associated tools: status in 2013 (1)
Tips (3)
Tissue (7)
Tissue Array (6)
Tubes (3)
Tags2016 update of the PRIDE database and its related tools
ACAA1
and PXMP4 in Peroxisome Pathway Are Down-Regulated and Have Clinical Significance in Non-small Cell Lung Cancer.
dynabeads c1
dynabeads cd8
dynabeads cd19 pan b
Experimental data from flesh quality assessment and shelf life monitoring of high pressure processed European sea bass (Dicentrarchus labrax) fillets.
High-throughput protein localization in Arabidopsis using Agrobacterium-mediated transient expression of GFP-ORF fusions
HSD17B4
MAGNA MEDICS
MagSi-proteomics
MD01009
MD01014
MD01015
MD02014
MD02015
MINT
Proteomic analysis and interactions network in leaves of mycorrhizal and nonmycorrhizal sorghum plants under water deficit.
The Gene Ontology Annotation (GOA) Database: sharing knowledge in Uniprot with Gene Ontology
The genome sequence of Bifidobacterium longum subsp. infantis reveals adaptations for milk utilization within the infant microbiome
the molecular interaction database: 2012 update
The ProteomeXchange consortium in 2017: supporting the cultural change in proteomics public data deposition
The PRoteomics IDEntifications (PRIDE) database and associated tools: status in 2013
Recent Posts
Magnetic Beads Proteomics
MagSi proteomics
Protease Guide For Tag Removal
Proteomics Ressources Plugins
Experimental data from flesh quality assessment and shelf life monitoring of high pressure processed European sea bass (Dicentrarchus labrax) fillets.
ScyTek LaboratoriesFollowScyTek Laboratories@ScytekLab·18 Julhttps://lnkd.in/gr_iHgbReply on Twitter 1284453523514482688Retweet on Twitter 1284453523514482688Like on Twitter 1284453523514482688Twitter 1284453523514482688ScyTek Laboratories@ScytekLab·18 Julhttps://lnkd.in/grBmH2dReply on Twitter 1284452520899702785Retweet on Twitter 1284452520899702785Like on Twitter 1284452520899702785Twitter 1284452520899702785ScyTek Laboratories@ScytekLab·4 Sep 2019Human ovary tissue stained with Cytokeratin 7; Clone OV-TL12/30 using PolyTek Anti-Mouse with DAB.
Magnification 200X.
Available at https://www.scytek.com/products/39.56-A00142-0002-Cytokeratin-7-Clone-OV-TL12-30-(Ready-To-Use).asp
Cat#:
A00142 Reply on Twitter 1169374054085611520Retweet on Twitter 11693740540856115203Like on Twitter 11693740540856115204Twitter 1169374054085611520ScyTek Laboratories@ScytekLab·31 Jul 2019Human Tonsil stained with CD75 (B-Cell Marker); Clone LN1 using PolyTek Anti-Mouse with DAB.
Magnification 100X.
Available at https://www.scytek.com/products/103.1-A00047-CD75-Clone-LN1.asp
Cat#:
A00047 Reply on Twitter 1156677089136795648Retweet on Twitter 11566770891367956483Like on Twitter 11566770891367956483Twitter 1156677089136795648Retweet on TwitterScyTek Laboratories RetweetedScyTek Laboratories@ScytekLab·20 Jun 2019Mouse Brain stained using PolyTek Anti-Mouse & GFAP; Clone ASTRO/789.
Magnification 400X.
Available at https://www.scytek.com/products/88.09-PAM008-PolyTek-Anti-Mouse-Polymerized-HRP.asp
Cat#:
PAM & A00158 Reply on Twitter 1141816495019683840Retweet on Twitter 11418164950196838404Like on Twitter 11418164950196838404Twitter 1141816495019683840Load More...
